# **Matthias Wens**

Staf van elzenlaan 30, 2550 Kontich, Belgium +32497 28 23 22 | matthias\_wens@hotmail.com



#### **PROFILE**

Name: Matthias Wens

Address: Staf van elzenlaan 30, 2550 Kontich, Belgium

• Phone: +32 497 28 23 22

• E-mail: matthias\_wens@hotmail.com

• Date of birth: 22-08-1995

Place of birth: Wilrijk, Belgium

• Nationality: Belgian

• Gender: Male

• Marital Status: Single

# **PROFILE**

I am an engaged student in Master of Electronics and ICT Engineering Technology at KULeuven. I have an advanced skillset in Python programming and have leadership experiences. I am currently searching for a student job in python or java developing.

#### **EDUCATION**

# KULeuven, Campus De Nayer

Sint-katelijne-waver, Belgium

Master of Electronics and ICT Engineering Technology (not yet finished)

2014-2018

Bachelor of ICT Engineering (not finished)

Heverlee, Belgium

Bacholol of tot Engineering (not innertea)

2013-2014

Sint-ritacollege

**KULeuven** 

Kontich, Belgium

Grieks-wiskunde

2007-2013

# **EXPERIENCE**

/

# OTHER EXPERIENCE

### E-kring

Sint-katelijne-waver, Belgium

Chief of Course documents store (Cursusdienst)

2016-2017

- Communication with professors and assistants.
- Making sure that fellow-students receive printed course documents after they ordered and paid for them.
- Participating in the meetings of the center-group of the organization (Praesidium).
- Helping with built-up, clean-up, ... of activities.

#### **Schoolrock Festival**

Kontich, Belgium

Coördinator 2012-2013

- Leading function in the organisation of Schoolrock Festival, a festival organised by approximately 90 students of Sint-ritacollege, Kontich, Belgium
- Follow up the different working groups of students.
- Leading the meetings of the center-group of the organization.
- Participate in meetings with police, fire department, municipality, mayor, school principal, ...
- Coordinate the different events during the building of the festival, the festival itself and the clean-up afterwards.

# **Schoolrock Festival**

Kontich, Belgium

Co-operator Terrain unit / Chief of Main Entrance

2011-2012

- Participating in meeting of the working group "Terrein".
- Placing orders for stages, Pa installations, ...
- Responsible for the Entrance, Personal search and Ticketing control during the Festival. Leading function over approximately 20 students.
- Participate in built-up and clean-up of the festival.

# **SKILLS**

- Dutch (Mother language)
- Good understanding of both written and spoken English
- Conversational in French

- Holding a full car driver's license.
- Advanced level skills in Microsoft Office Suite/Libre Office.
- Programming: Python2/3 (100%), Java (95%), SQL (75%), HTML (90%), CSS (85%), Assembly (80%), VHDL (100%), C (80%), JavaScript (60%), PHP (60%)

# **HONOR & AWARD**

# Winner of Google Hashcode in the Antwerp Hub

Antwerp, Belgium

Google (Hosted by Taglayer)

2017

Winner of the online qualification round of Google Hashcode in the Antwerp Hub.

#### **OTHER**

Kazou vzw Antwerp, Belgium

Animator 2011-now

Accompany and animate children aged 15-16 on a vacation.

Creactief vzw Mortsel, Belgium

Swimming Instructor 2011-now

Teaching children (Ages 4-14) to swim

**Judoclub Kim-budo** Kontich, Belgium

Judo assistant Trainer 2010-now

Helping the trainer with the judo trainings.

Training the youngest group of judoka's.

# **HOBBY**

- Rock climber
- Pianist and guitarist